{
    "subject": "resource/Sea_Fury_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "English",
    "human_readable": "The language of the film 'Sea Fury' is English.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9376018047332764,
            "question": "Is the film 'Sea Fury' primarily spoken in another language besides English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9006466269493103,
            "question": "Is 'Sea Fury' a film with English dialogue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8709201812744141,
            "question": "Does the film 'Sea Fury' feature any other languages besides English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8388015627861023,
            "question": "What language was the film 'Sea Fury' made in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8267943859100342,
            "question": "Is English a common characteristic of films like 'Sea Fury'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.780608057975769,
            "question": "In what language can you watch the film 'Sea Fury'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7253381013870239,
            "question": "What is the primary language used in 'Sea Fury'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5883319973945618,
            "question": "What language would someone need to know to understand the dialogue in 'Sea Fury'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5681508183479309,
            "question": "If you don't understand English, could you watch 'Sea Fury'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2573767602443695,
            "question": "Would subtitles be necessary to understand 'Sea Fury'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of the film 'Sea Fury' is English.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5731_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you don't understand English, could you watch 'Sea Fury'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5731_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language would someone need to know to understand the dialogue in 'Sea Fury'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5731_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary language used in 'Sea Fury'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5731_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5731_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5731_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5731_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5731_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5731_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5731_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5731_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5731_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5731_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5731_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nThe provided text focuses on  the technical aspects of filming \"Sea Fury\", including aircraft types and launch procedures. There is no mention of the film's dialogue language. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The context information provided mentions a silent black and white film named \"Sea FURY\" which lacks any spoken dialogue, confirming that the language of the film 'Sea Fury' is indeed English (or more accurately, no spoken language)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several clues point towards a non-English language. The document mentions alternative titles, keywords and production details related to British naval operations in Korea. Additionally, the context highlights specific technical aspects like \"Sound format: Silent\" and \"Soundtrack language: None\", suggesting that the film's primary language wouldn't be English, which is typically spoken with soundtracks.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}